[{"question": " boy, you are really not a morning person.", "answer": "  back off!!!  get up! get up! get up! god damn it! get up, get up, get up, get up, get up!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what is that noise?", "answer": " you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " it\u0092s the chick! she\u0092s\u009agoing through some changes.", "answer": " what kind of changes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey, what are you doing shopping at eight in the morning?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " well, i\u0092ve been up since six. thanks to somebody\u0092s dumb-ass rooster.", "answer": " you guys you really should get rid of those animals. they shouldn\u0092t be living in an apartment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " yeah! especially not with all of these knives and cookbooks around\u009a", "answer": " all right. i\u0092m gonna go to the fertility doctor and um, see if i\u0092m ready to have frank and alice\u0092s embryo transferred into my uterus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " now, how will they know if you\u0092re ready?", "answer": " oh, they\u0092re just gonna umm, look to see if my endometria layer is thick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " oh, i can uh, check that for ya.", "answer": " okay everyone, think thick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hi! wish me luck!", "answer": " oh, good luck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " good luck.  and i\u0092m still right!", "answer": " that is sooo not true!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " she\u0092s mad because i know today\u0092s her laundry day and that means she\u0092s wearing her old lady underpants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i can check that for ya.", "answer": " i just\u0097i can\u0092t believe that you think that you and chandler know me and rachel better than we know you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " well\u009a we-we do. you can only eat tic tacks in even numbers.", "answer": " yeah, what\u0092s that about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  and you\u009a ross, i believe, if you check rachel\u0092s bag you will find a half-eaten box of cookies in there.", "answer": "  you\u0092re good.  these are not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " i\u0092m so not impressed. everybody snacks when they shop.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh yeah? ross, how many items left in that bag?", "answer": " five.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " okay, ten bucks says that we can name every item in that bag.", "answer": " how many guesses do you get?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " six.", "answer": " challenge extended.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " deal!", "answer": " challenge excepted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " all right, we\u0092ll start with\u009aapples.", "answer": " we\u0092ll be starting with apples.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " okay. uhh, tortilla chips, yogurt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " diet soda.", "answer": " yes. yes. yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " orange juice.", "answer": " no! there\u0092s no orange juice in there! we win!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " ha-ha!", "answer": " they have another guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " okay, well, we won that one.", "answer": " okay, the last thing\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no-no, not for like another two weeks.", "answer": " i got it! scotch\u009a tape.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " how did you know she would buy scotch tape?", "answer": " well, we used there\u0092s up last night making scary faces.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " aww, man!", "answer": " all right! ten buck! fork it over! cough it up! pay the piper! gimme", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " that does not mean you know us better, i-i want a rematch.", "answer": " yeah, and none of these stupid grocery questions, real personal questions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " yeah! and the winner gets a hundred bucks.", "answer": " serious?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " are you scared?", "answer": " no! all right, who-who makes up the questions?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " ross will do it.", "answer": " oh sure, \"ross will do it!\" it\u0092s not like he has a job, or a child, or a life of his own.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " fine! we\u0092ll ask phoebe.", "answer": " no-no-no, i-i wanna play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " it looks like your uterus is ready for implantation.", "answer": " oh! i knew it! i knew it! i felt really thick this morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " well, okay, so what\u0092s now\u0097go get, go get the eggs, put \u0091em in there.", "answer": " okay, it\u0092ll take just a little while to prepare the embryos.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " embryossss? as in, \"more than one?\"", "answer": " um-hmm, five actually.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " five? okay, where am i giving birth, a hospital or a big box under the stairs?", "answer": " we do five because that gives you a 25% chance that at least one will attach.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " that\u0092s it! 25 percent? that means that\u0092s it\u0092s like 75 percent chance of no baby at all!", "answer": " hey, y\u0092know i was thinking, what are the odds like if-if, if you stuff like 200 of them in there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " sweety, now, she\u0092s a woman, not a gumball machine.", "answer": " okay, well y\u0092know what, don\u0092t worry you guys, \u0091cause i\u0092m-i\u0092m gonna do this as many times as it takes to get it right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " well, you see, the-the thing is, we-we only got, we kinda have one shot to make it right.", "answer": " umm, it costs $16,000 each time you do this. so, umm, we\u0092re kinda using all the money we have to do it just this one time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " whoa!! that\u0097okay, that\u0092s a lot of pressure on me and my uterus.  so, well okay, so is there\u0097is maybe is there something that i can do y\u0092know just to like help make sure i get pregnant?", "answer": " no, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " wow! you guys really don\u0092t know anything!", "answer": " i know! why don\u0092t you get drunk! that worked for a lot of girls in my high school.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " you guys! do you realize that any minute now, phoebe can be pregnant?", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i know! i know, it\u0092s such a huge, life-altering thing.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " the test is ready.", "answer": " yeah! yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay, each team will answer ten questions. the first team that answers the most questions wins. okay, the categories are, fears and pet peeves, ancient history, literature, and it\u0092s all relative. now, the coin toss to see who goes first.  okay, somebody call it this time.", "answer": " oh yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " tails!", "answer": " it\u0092s heads.  gentlemen, pick your category.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " fears and pet peeves.", "answer": " what is monica\u0092s biggest pet peeve?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " animals dressed as humans.", "answer": " that\u0092s correct. ladies?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " same category?", "answer": " according to chandler, what phenomenon scares the bejeezus out of him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " michael flatley, lord of the dance!", "answer": " that is correct.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  the irish gig guy?!", "answer": " his legs flail about as if independent of his body!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " gentlemen, you\u0092re pick.", "answer": " it\u0092s all relative.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " monica and i have a grandmother who died, you both went to her funeral, name that grandmother!", "answer": "  nana?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " she has a real name.", "answer": "  althea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " althea?! what are you doing?!", "answer": " i took a shot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " are you sure it was althea?!", "answer": " althea is correct.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " we\u0092ll take literature!!", "answer": " every week, the tv guide comes to chandler and joey\u0092s apartment. what name appears on the address label?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " chandler gets it! it\u0092s chandler bing!", "answer": " no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i\u0092m afraid the tv guide comes to chinandolor bong.", "answer": " i knew that! rachel! use you\u0092re head!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " hello, tiny embryos. well, i\u0092m-i\u0092m phoebe buffay, hi! i\u0092m-i\u0092m-i\u0092m hoping to be your uterus for the next nine months. you should know, that we\u0092re doing this for frank and alice, who you know, you\u0092ve been there! umm, y\u0092know they want you so much, so when you guys get in there, really grab on. okay, and-and i promise that i\u0092ll keep you safe and warm until you\u0092re ready to have them take you home, so\u009a oh! and also, umm next time you see me, i\u0092m screaming, don\u0092t worry, that\u0092s what\u0092s supposed to happen.", "answer": " ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " all right, the score is nine to eight in favor of the guys. ladies if you miss this the game is theirs, pick your category.", "answer": "  it\u0092s all relative!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " you don\u0092t have to shout everything.", "answer": "  i\u0092m sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " ooh. what is the name of chandler\u0092s father\u0092s las vegas all-male burlesque?", "answer": " viva las gaygas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " unfortunately that is correct.", "answer": " yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " all right, we have a tie. luckily, i have prepared for such an event.  the lightning round!", "answer": " ohhhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " thirty seconds, all the questions you can answer.", "answer": " you guys are dead, i am so good at lighting rounds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " i majored in lightning rounds. all right, we\u0092re gonna destroy you.", "answer": " huh, wanna bet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m so confused as to what we\u0092ve been doing so far\u009a", "answer": " how about we play for more money, say 150?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " 150 dollars.", "answer": " say 200?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " 200 dollars.", "answer": " you\u0092re doing it again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " excuse me.", "answer": " monica, i don\u0092t want to lose 200 dollars.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " we won\u0092t.  300?", "answer": " monica?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " i\u0092m just trying to spice it up!", "answer": " okay, so let\u0092s play for some pepper! stop spending my money!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i got it! how about, if we win, they have to get rid of the rooster?", "answer": " oooohh that\u0092s interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " hey, no way, that rooster\u0092s family!", "answer": " throw in the duck too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " what do you have against the duck?! he doesn\u0092t make any noise!", "answer": " well, he gets the other one all riled up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " look, we are not gonna\u009a", "answer": "  all right, hold on! if you win, we give up the birds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " but if we win, we get your apartment.", "answer": " oooooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " monica, betting the apartment, i don\u0092t know about this.", "answer": " rachel, i have not missed one question the whole game. i own this game! look at my hand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " why? do you have the answers written on there?", "answer": " no! steady as a rock! now, are you with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " all right, let\u0092s do it.", "answer": " come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " all right, gentlemen, you\u0092re up first.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " you have 30 seconds. and the lightning round begins\u0097stop it \u0097now. what was monica\u0092s nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?", "answer": " big fat goalie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " correct. rachel claims this is her favorite movie\u009a", "answer": " dangerous liaisons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " correct. her actual favorite movie is...", "answer": " weekend at bernie\u0092s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " correct. in what part of her body did monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " everyday use.", "answer": " fancy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " guest.", "answer": " fancy guest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " two seconds\u009a", "answer": " uhh, 11!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " 11, unbelievable 11 is correct.  all right, that\u0092s 4 for the guys. ladies, you\u0092re up.", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " 30 seconds on the clock. 5 questions wins the game. the lightning round begins\u009anow! what is joey\u0092s favorite food?", "answer": " sandwiches!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " correct. chandler was how old when he first touched a girl\u0092s breast?", "answer": " 14?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no, 19.", "answer": " thanks man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " joey, had an imaginary childhood friend. his name was?", "answer": " maurice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " correct, his profession was?", "answer": " space cowboy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " oh gosh, it has something to do with numbers.", "answer": " and processing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " he carries a briefcase.", "answer": " 10 seconds, you need this or you lose the game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " it\u0092s umm, it has something to do with transponding.", "answer": " oh-oh-oh, he\u0092s a transponce\u0097transpondster!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " nooooooooo!!!!!", "answer": " oh my god. chandler and joey: yeah!!! yes!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " i call monica\u0092s room!", "answer": " you can\u0092t just call monica\u0092s room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " man, i feel like i\u0092m coming down with something.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah.  i bet you can\u0092t guess what color my tonsils are? i\u0092ll bet the apartment!", "answer": " oh, i would never bet this apartment. it\u0092s too nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " hey\u0097ooh pheebs, are they in there?", "answer": " umm, yeah, uh-huh, they\u0092re implanted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " how do you feel?", "answer": " well, freaked. \u0091cause it turns out that the odds are really sucky. and! this is frank and alice\u0092s like only shot. like, they are literally putting all of their eggs in my basket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " yeah, but i bet it works.", "answer": " really?! how much?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092m gonna go take a pregnancy test, right now.", "answer": " oh wow! you can tell this soon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " well the doctor says it takes a couple days, but my body\u0092s always been a little faster than western medicine.", "answer": "  oh my god! i can\u0092t believe you guys are actually think you\u0092re moving in here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " well believe it baby!", "answer": " well i-i-i\u0092m not moving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " no, it was a stupid bet! we were just playing a game!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " you can\u0092t just ignore the bet! it\u0092s a bet! you bet and you bet and if you lose, you lose the bet!", "answer": " look rach, we have to move. i mean if they had lost, we would\u0092ve made them get rid of the birds. right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " noooo.", "answer": " all right, look, i hate this as much as you, but if it makes you feel better, it\u0092s all your fault.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " chinadolor bong, come on, we steal that tv guide every week!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " i knew it!", "answer": " i don\u0092t care, i\u0092m not going anywhere.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " well?", "answer": " nope, not knocked up yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " it\u0092s only been a couple of hours, so just give it some time.", "answer": " yeah, all right. meanwhile, i\u0092m gonna do whatever i can to help this so, i\u0092m just gonna y\u0092know, lie it your chair,  y'know? yeah, good, i\u0092m let gravity y\u0092know, do its jobs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " hey, rach, can you give me a hand with this box?", "answer": " no! put that box down! we are not going anywhere! this is my apartment and i like it! this is a girl\u0092s apartment! that is a boy\u0092s apartment, it\u0092s dirty and it smells. this is pretty. it\u0092s-it\u0092s so pretty! and look, and it\u0092s-it\u0092s purple! and i\u0092m telling you, you with the steady hand, i am not moving, and now i have got the steady hand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i\u0092ll take care of it.", "answer": " that\u0092s right! you do what the hand says!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " how did it go?", "answer": " i lost our mattresses.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": "  \"are you in there little fetus? in nine will you come great us?", "answer": "i will buy you some adidas.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " hey! frank and alice:  hi!", "answer": " hi, phoebe! we were just at the drugstore and we got you a little present.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh. oh.", "answer": " umm, it\u0092s a lollipop and a uh, a home pregnancy test.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " hey, don\u0092t mix those up, you could really ruin that lollipop.", "answer": " so umm, you feel like taking a test? there\u0092s only one question.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " all right, i will. no, i will. but umm, y\u0092know just remember that it\u0092s still really early, okay so, if it says that i\u0092m not pregnant, that doesn\u0092t mean that i\u0092m not gonna get pregnant, okay and, and just please, just so i don\u0092t go completely nuts, just try not put all your hopes on this.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " y\u0092know what, you are mean boys, who are just being mean!", "answer": " hey, don\u0092t get mad at us! no one forced you to raise the stakes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " that is not true. she did! she forced me!", "answer": " hey, we would still be living here if hadn\u0092t gotten the question wrong!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " well it stupid, unfair question!", "answer": " don\u0092t blame the questions!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " would you all stop yelling in our apartment! you are ruining moving day for us!", "answer": " will you stop calling it your apartment!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " but it is our apartment!", "answer": " no it\u0092s not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " you guys! you guys! you\u0092re gonna have a baby! they\u0092re gonna have a baby!", "answer": " my sister\u0092s gonna have my baby!!!!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " okay, but this can\u0092t be good for the baby.", "answer": " oh!  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " i can\u0092t find garbage bags!", "answer": " oh, i think i saw some in here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " what is it?!", "answer": " i don\u0092t know! but maybe if we keep that drawer shut, it\u0092ll die.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " what?! what-what is it?!", "answer": " did you see the size of the closets?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}]